<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AstroGPS</string>
    <string name="app_version">اصدار التطبيق النسخة 1.0</string>

    <string name="about_us_title_1">AstroGPS</string>
    <string name="about_us_des_1">
    This app works with Astro GPS Tracking Devices Series, i.e. Astro101, Astro201, Astro301, Astro401 and Astro400e (all devices are available at www.tomotek.com.cn)
        Astro Devices are the newest GPS tracking innovation from TOMO Tech. The super simple Astro GPS mobile application with an esthetically designed user interface (UI), giving the Astro solution a much more user friendly experience.
        \nThe platform consists of:
        \n -A very simple Mobile application (Astro GPS App), with monitoring and reporting functionality.
        \n -The main solution screens, can be browsed using PC web browser, give full accessibility to system admin, including users management, reports, screens, full solution control.
        \n -The user end Astro devices, to be attached to the targeted vehicle.
        \n -An extendable database, which ultimately can meet various functional requirements and needs.
        \n\n With Astro GPS Solution, your vehicle will be upgraded to be smart as you like it.
        \n Our devices are compatible with all kind of vehicles cars, trucks, jet skis, Engines or even non-enginic equipments.
    </string>
    <string name="google_maps_keys">AIzaSyCsMtq5YIRGwrU-dWC5CsycyQ--6tOwuo0</string>
    <!--<string name="google_maps_keys">AIzaSyB8CaFPkBKNnwrke1TZQzJB-CNp5NF8PtI</string>-->

    <string name="about_us_title_2">Busy? No problem, Astro GPS Solution and applications will simplify monitoring and controlling your fleet everywhere at anytime.</string>

    <string name="about_us_des_2">
        - Real-time fleet locations:
        \n Make better decisions with accurate information updated every minute.
        \n\n - Accurate usage reports:
        \n Reduce paperwork and human error. Generate reports that can show you comparison of vehicle usage.
        \n\n - Utilize assets:
        \n Reports will help you identify underutilized and overutilized vehicles
        \n\n - Bill customers of leased equipment:
        \n Get reports on the hours leased equipment was operated. Or even if it was operated on holidays
        \n\n - Reduce the rate of accidents:
        \n Improve the driving behaviors of your employees, improve your employee safety while reducing maintenance costs.
        \n That’s not even everything! Customized sensor solutions,  Trip tracking, vehicle insights, a web dashboard and more are all included.
    </string>

    <string name="saferoad_website">موقع AstroGPS</string>

    <string name="are_you_sure_do_want_to_exit_saferoad">Are you sure you want to exit AstroGPS?</string>

</resources>
